<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=16] -->
    <string name="app_name">Rohtak Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Category name for restaurants [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for hotels [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>

    <!-- Category name for places to visit [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_places_to_visit">Places to Visit</string>

    <!-- Category name for cities nearby [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_cities_nearby">Cities Nearby</string>

    <!-- **************************************************** -->

    <!-- Location data for Restaurants Category -->

    <string name="restaurants_gulab_name">Gulab Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurants_gulab_address">NH-10, Near Sheela Bypass Chowk</string>
    <string name="restaurants_gulab_description">Sweets, Fast Food, North-Indian Cuisine. World
        famous for unique and wide range of Rewri, Gajaks and Chikkis. Manufacturers, retailers and
        exporters of Rewri, Gajjak, Sweets, Namkeens and other related products.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_fouji_name">Fouji Dhaba</string>
    <string name="restaurants_fouji_address">59th Milestone, NH-10, Delhi-Rohtak Road</string>
    <string name="restaurants_fouji_description">North-Indian Cuisine, Vegetarian-Friendly. Hot and
        fresh food, round the corner. With vast parking area, you get value of your money.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_pandit_name">Pandit Chat Bhandar</string>
    <string name="restaurants_pandit_address">Delhi Road, Near Raj Cinema</string>
    <string name="restaurants_pandit_description">Indian/Chinese Fast Food. Dahi Bhalle, Aloo Tikki,
        Pav Bhaaji, Cholle Bhature Pizza, Dosa and more yummy food.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_mcdonalds_name">McDonalds</string>
    <string name="restaurants_mcdonalds_address">Delhi Road, Opp. Power House Office</string>
    <string name="restaurants_mcdonalds_description">McDonalds Fast Food Joint. Classic,
        long-running fast-food chain known for its burgers, fries and shakes.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_subway_name">Subway</string>
    <string name="restaurants_subway_address">Dev Colony, Delhi Road</string>
    <string name="restaurants_subway_description">The Subway brand is the world\'s largest submarine
    sandwich chain. It is a casual counter-serve chain for made-to-order sandwiches and
        salads.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_apsara_name">Apsara Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurants_apsara_address">Sector 1, Delhi Bypass Chowk</string>
    <string name="restaurants_apsara_description">Multi-Cuisine Restaurant. Serves breakfast,
        lunch, dinner, coffee and drinks.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_dominos_name">Dominos</string>
    <string name="restaurants_dominos_address">Ground Floor, Rohtak-Sonipat Road,
        Skytech Mall</string>
    <string name="restaurants_dominos_description">Delivery/carryout chain offering a wide range
        of pizza, plus chicken and other sides.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_cafe_coffee_name">Cafe Coffee Day</string>
    <string name="restaurants_cafe_coffee_address">Ground Floor, Rohtak-Sonipat Road,
        Skytech Mall</string>
    <string name="restaurants_cafe_coffee_description">Café Coffee Day is a coffee shop for the
        young and the young at heart. We source our coffees from thousands of small coffee
        planters.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_pizza_wings_name">Pizza Wings</string>
    <string name="restaurants_pizza_wings_address">NH-10, Near Sheela Bypass Chowk</string>
    <string name="restaurants_pizza_wings_description">Pizza Wings is about much more than pizzas.
        From freshly sauteed pastas and delicious appetizers to mocktails, desserts, soups and
        salads, they have a wide range for you to feast on.</string>

    <string name="restaurants_360_degrees_name">360 Degrees Breweries and Grill</string>
    <string name="restaurants_360_degrees_address">1st Floor, Rohtak-Sonipat Road,
        Skytech Mall</string>
    <string name="restaurants_360_degrees_description">The most happening lounge club cum night
        club of Rohtak. Offers fresh beer with renowned DJ\'s and fully loaded bar.</string>

    <!-- **************************************************** -->

    <!-- Location data for Hotels Category -->

    <string name="hotels_d2m_name">D2M Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotels_d2m_address">Sangum Complex, Near New Bus Stand
        \n\nCall: +91-1262-255-777</string>
    <string name="hotels_d2m_description">Convention Hall, Conference Facility, Parking Facility,
        Travel Counter, Banquet Facility, Internet Access, Doctor-on-call, Air-Conditioning,
        In-room Electronic Safe, Two In-house Multi-cuisine Restaurants Maharaja and Royala</string>

    <string name="hotels_rivoli_name">Hotel Rivoli</string>
    <string name="hotels_rivoli_address">Chanakya Puri, Sonipat Road, Near Sheela Bypass
        \n\nCall: +91-92543-88828</string>
    <string name="hotels_rivoli_description">Free High-Speed Internet (WiFi), Room Service,
        In-house Restaurant, Free Parking, Conference Hall, Banquet Hall</string>

    <string name="hotels_crystal_name">Hotel Crystal Continental</string>
    <string name="hotels_crystal_address">Sheela Bye-Pass, Delhi Road
        \n\nCall: +91-1262-274572</string>
    <string name="hotels_crystal_description">In-room Dining, Air Conditioning, WiFi Internet,
        In-room Safety Deposit Locker, Travel Desk, Wheel-chair Access, Doctor-on-call, Banquet
        Facilities, In-house Multi-cuisine Restaurant, Free Parking</string>

    <string name="hotels_sagar_name">Hotel Sagar Villa</string>
    <string name="hotels_sagar_address">Sheela Bye-Pass, Delhi Road
        \n\nCall: +91-92158-20008</string>
    <string name="hotels_sagar_description">In-house Restaurant, Free Parking, WiFi, Air
        Conditioning, In-house Bar</string>

    <string name="hotels_harjais_name">Hotel Harjais</string>
    <string name="hotels_harjais_address">Rohtak Habitat Center, Opp. Tilyar Lake, NH-10
        \n\nCall: +91-98120-08642</string>
    <string name="hotels_harjais_description">WiFi, Air Conditioning, Swimming Pool, Parking,
        Meeting/Conference Room, Gym/Fitness Centre</string>

    <string name="hotels_platinum_name">Hotel Platinum Plaza</string>
    <string name="hotels_platinum_address">Sector-14, Main Market
        \n\nCall: +91-93548-11000</string>
    <string name="hotels_platinum_description">In-house Restaurant, Travel Desk, Doctor-on-call,
        Business Centre, Parking Facility, Air-Conditioning, WiFi Internet, Complimentary Breakfast,
        Gym, In-room Mini Bar</string>

    <string name="hotels_royal_name">Hotel Royal Mall</string>
    <string name="hotels_royal_address">Sector-14, Main Market
        \n\nCall: +91-92153-31448</string>
    <string name="hotels_royal_description">Free Parking, WiFi, Air Conditioning, Convention Hall,
        Laptop-on-demand, Fax and Copier Service, Medical Assistance, Travel Desk, Car Rental
        Services</string>

    <string name="hotels_glassee_name">Hotel Glassee</string>
    <string name="hotels_glassee_address">D-Park, Near Sate Bank of Patiala
        \n\nCall: +91-92156-61110</string>
    <string name="hotels_glassee_description">In-house Restaurant, Travel Counter, In-room Mini
        Bar, Air Conditioning</string>

    <!-- **************************************************** -->

    <!-- Location data for Places to Visit Category -->

    <string name="ptv_tilyar_lake_name">Tilyar Lake</string>
    <string name="ptv_tilyar_lake_address">NH-10, Rohtak-Delhi Highway</string>
    <string name="ptv_tilyar_lake_description">Tilyar Lake is one of the major tourist attractions
        in the Indian state of Haryana. Fishing is permissible at Tilyar Lake after paying INR200
        fishing fee. The lake lies in a 132-acre (0.53 km2) area and forms an integral part of the
        tourist setup, making it one of the greenest stretches in the adjoining area. The spacious
        lawns and the scenery on view make this resort a great place to relax, and people visit
        from as far away as Mumbai. It is also an excellent spot for watching a variety of birds
        that flock on the little island located in the middle of the lake. ENtry to Tilyar lake
        is free.</string>

    <string name="ptv_tilyar_zoo_name">Tilyar Zoo</string>
    <string name="ptv_tilyar_zoo_address">NH-10, Rohtak-Delhi Highway</string>
    <string name="ptv_tilyar_zoo_description">Visitor facilities include landscaping, walkways and
        trails, gardens, hillocks, lakes, artificial waterfalls, cafe, visitor toilets and resting
        shelters, watch towers, drinking water facilities etc. Entry is only INR10 for adults and
        INR5 for kids.</string>

    <string name="ptv_banni_name">Banni Khera Farm</string>
    <string name="ptv_banni_address">Village Samar Gopalpur, Jind Bypass</string>
    <string name="ptv_banni_description">The farm house is spread over 10 acres of land. It is
        designed as per the Vaastu Shastra. Farming is a year round occupation with a variety of
        activities occurring throughout the year. Visitors are welcome to explore the haveli at
        Banni Khera Farms and fields at leisure. Its tranquil location is enhanced by on-site
        fishing. The exclusive setting makes it an ideal place for people seeking an experience,
        of true ethnic and cultural ethos and exposure of modern-day farming in India.</string>

    <string name="ptv_merion_name">Merion Sky Mall</string>
    <string name="ptv_merion_address">Sector 3, Sonepat Road</string>
    <string name="ptv_merion_description">There are a wide range of clothing shops, restaurants
        and food court in Skytech Mall where one can splurge into great delicacies. There\'s
        availability of multiplexes too, so if not interested in shopping, movies are the best
        option to go for.</string>

    <string name="ptv_splash_name">Splash Water World</string>
    <string name="ptv_splash_address">Rajeev Nagar</string>
    <string name="ptv_splash_description">Slash is nestled in natural beauty with a backdrop of
        cooling shelter of trees. An idyllic hideaway, Splash offers matchless excitement and
        promises a whole lot of fun time with water slides, stimulated Rain Dances and Wave Pool.
        Splash brings you a variety of ultramodern water slides and rides that thrill you and
        dip you in ecstatic Splash experience. A pollution free atmosphere combined with
        international standards of safety provides absolute privacy to couples and family and
        is a suitable venue to spend some quality time with your loved ones.</string>

    <string name="ptv_sai_name">Sai Temple</string>
    <string name="ptv_sai_address">NH-10 Rohtak-Delhi Highway</string>
    <string name="ptv_sai_description">This is very popular in the area and once can see long
        queues on Thursday here. People come here with their wishes and to get blessings of
        Sai.</string>

    <string name="ptv_mansarovar_name">Mansarovar Park</string>
    <string name="ptv_mansarovar_address">Mansarovar Colony, Delhi Road</string>
    <string name="ptv_mansarovar_description">The Mansarovar Park is located in the core of the
        city where visitors can avail hotels or resorts for their stay and visit the park
        frequently for the relaxation. The reward should go to the Municipal Corporation of
        Haryana that has constructed this park and are maintaining it beautifully.</string>

    <string name="ptv_gufa_name">Gufa Wala Temple</string>
    <string name="ptv_gufa_address">Char-Khamba, Model Town</string>
    <string name="ptv_gufa_description">A famous temple in the city with a small cave(gufa) as
        its special attraction.</string>

    <!-- **************************************************** -->

    <!-- Location data for Cities Nearby Category -->

    <string name="cities_delhi_name">New Delhi</string>
    <string name="cities_delhi_address">66km (1h 40m) from Rohtak</string>
    <string name="cities_delhi_description">New Delhi is the capital of India and one of Delhi
        city\'s 11 districts. The foundation stone of the city was laid by George V, Emperor of
        India during the Delhi Durbar of 1911. It was designed by British architects, Sir Edwin
        Lutyens and Sir Herbert Baker. The new capital was inaugurated on 13 February 1931, by
        Viceroy and Governor-General of India Lord Irwin.
        \n\nAlthough colloquially Delhi and New Delhi as names are used interchangeably to refer to
        the jurisdiction of the National Capital Territory (NCT) of Delhi, these are two distinct
        entities, and the latter is a small part of the former. New Delhi has been selected as one
        of the hundred Indian cities to be developed as a smart city under PM Narendra Modi\'s
        flagship Smart Cities Mission.</string>

    <string name="cities_chandigarh_name">Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="cities_chandigarh_address">240km (3h 30m) from Rohtak</string>
    <string name="cities_chandigarh_description">Chandigarh is a city and a union territory of
        India that serves as the capital of the Indian states of Punjab and Haryana. As a union
        territory, the city is governed directly by the Union Government and is not part of either
        state.
        \n\nChandigarh is bordered by the state of Punjab to the north, west and south, and to the
        state of Haryana to the east. Chandigarh is considered to be a part of the Chandigarh
        capital region or Greater Chandigarh, which includes Chandigarh, and the cities of Mohali,
        Zirakpur, Kharar, Kurali (in Punjab) and the city of Panchkula (in Haryana).
        \n\nChandigarh was one of the early planned cities in the post-independence India and is
        internationally known for its architecture and urban design. The master plan of the
        city was prepared by Swiss-French architect Le Corbusier, which transformed from earlier
        plans created by the Polish architect Maciej Nowicki and the American planner Albert Mayer.
        Most of the government buildings and housing in the city, were designed by the Chandigarh
        Capital Project Team headed by Le Corbusier, Jane Drew and Maxwell Fry. In 2015, an
        article published by BBC named Chandigarh as one of the perfect cities of the world in
        terms of architecture, cultural growth and modernisation.
        \n\nChandigarh’s Capitol Complex was in July 2016 declared by UNESCO as World Heritage at
        the 40th session of World Heritage Conference held in Istanbul. UNESCO inscription was
        under \"The Architectural Work of Le Corbusier an outstanding contribution to the
        Modern Movement\". The Capitol Complex buildings include the Punjab and Haryana High
        Court, Punjab and Haryana Secretariat and Punjab and Haryana Assembly along with monuments
        Open hand, Martyrs Memorial, Geometric Hill and Tower of Shadow.
        \n\nThe city was reported to be the cleanest in India in 2010, based on a national
        government study. In 2016, Chandigarh was declared as the second cleanest city of India
        under Swachh Bharat Survekshan. Chandigarh is also known to be the first smoke-free city
        in India.</string>


    <string name="cities_gurgaon_name">Gurgaon</string>
    <string name="cities_gurgaon_address">84km (1h 54m) from Rohtak</string>
    <string name="cities_gurgaon_description">Gurgaon, officially known as Gurugram, is a city in
        the Indian state of Haryana and is located near the National Capital Region of India. It
        is 32 kilometres (20 mi) southwest of New Delhi and 268 kilometres (167 mi) southwest of
        Chandigarh, the state capital. As of 2011, Gurgaon had a population of 876,824.
        \n\nWitnessing rapid urbanization, Gurgaon has become a leading financial and industrial
        hub with the third highest per capita income in India. Historically known as Gurugram, the
        city\'s economic growth story started when the leading Indian automobile manufacturer Maruti
        Suzuki India Limited established a manufacturing plant in Gurgaon in the 1970s. Today,
        Gurgaon has local offices for more than 250 Fortune 500 companies.</string>

    <string name="cities_panipat_name">Panipat</string>
    <string name="cities_panipat_address">77km (1h 18m) from Rohtak</string>
    <string name="cities_panipat_description">Panipat is an ancient and historic city in Haryana,
        India. It is 90 km north of Delhi and 169 km south of Chandigarh on NH-1. The battles
        fought at the city in 1526, 1556 and 1761 were turning points in Indian history. The city
        is famous in India by the name of \"City of Weavers\" and \"Textile City\".
    </string>

    <string name="cities_kurukshetra_name">Kurukshetra</string>
    <string name="cities_kurukshetra_address">150km (2h 14m) from Rohtak</string>
    <string name="cities_kurukshetra_description">Kurukshetra is a city in the state of Haryana,
        India. It is also known as Dharmakshetra (\"Holy Place\"). According to the
        Puranas, Kurukshetra is a region named after King Kuru, the ancestor of Kauravas and
        Pandavas, as depicted in epic Mahabharata. The importance of the place is attributed to
        the fact that the Kurukshetra War of the Mahabharata was fought on this land and the
        Bhagavad Gita was preached here during the war when Lord Krishna found Arjuna in a
        terrible dilemma.
        \n\nBefore the establishment of a refugee camp named Kurukshetra in 1947, Thanesar was the
        name of the tehsil headquarters and the town. Thanesar or Sthaneswar is a historical town
        located adjacent to what is now the newly created Kurukshetra city. Thanesar derives its
        name from the word \"Sthaneshwar\", which means \"Place of God\". The
        Sthaneshwar Mahadev Temple, whose presiding deity is Lord Shiva, is believed to be the
        oldest temple in the vicinity. Local hearsay identifies the legendary
        \"Kurukshetra\" with a place near Thanesar. A few kilometers from Kurukshetra
        is the village known as Amin, where there are remnants of a fort which is believed to be
        Abhimanyu\'s.
        \n\nIn most ancient Hindu texts, Kurukshetra is not a city but a region. The boundaries of
        Kurukshetra correspond roughly to the central and western parts of state of Haryana and
        southern Punjab. Thus according to the Taittiriya Aranyaka, the Kurukshetra region is
        south of Turghna (Srughna/Sugh in Sirhind, Punjab), north of Khandava (Delhi and Mewat
        region), east of Maru (desert) and west of Parin.
        \n\nIn early July 2013 the Haryana Department of Archaeology and Museums announced that
        the earlier excavated remains of a Buddhist stupa in Kurukshetra were ready to be displayed
        for the public.</string>

</resources>

